deltafx.com 2013-05-04

# Privacy Policy

#### Collection of Personal Information 

### 

The company is managed by the client, which is necessary for the customer, personal account opening request. Providing it is a necessary condition to protect the society to the interests of the customer and the customer transactions with a personal account, can run without concern about the asset security. The Company is entitled to information that can enhance their understanding of customer needs and preferences to collect. All necessary information for communication between the customer and the company is collected directly from customers.   
Use of Personal Information   

#### Personal Information

The company uses customer personal information for purposes of providing the client with safe, high quality service. Personal and contact information is received from the client uses to verify contact information and verify the identity of his clients. The company is also personal information to create accounts, open and modify trading accounts, issue activation codes and passwords to access. Client contact information will help the company improve its service and immediately inform the customer about the company more products, options and actions.   
Subsidiaries and Partners   

#### Partners

At the request of customers, the Company may provide information about services offered at the branches and partners. For the purpose of providing more quality services, the Company may make affiliate relationships or close marketing agreements with other companies. To provide the client with a full, well-timed and quality service, the Company may share information with partners and subsidiaries. The use of personal data of customers will be limited in this case.   
Disclosure of client information to third parties The Company may not disclose client described personal data except in the cases. The Company reserves the right to disclose personal information to third parties if required by law enforcement or other government authorities. The Company is entitled to charge the customer the information as necessary to provide tax or credit agencies or, in cases when the purpose of protecting the rights of the company and the property is required. If a third party receives personal information about a client, which it undertakes to describe this information in a manner similar to the way in protecting the privacy policy.   

#### Disclosure of Client Information

The company, a customer's personal data only for the purpose of improving the quality use of their services.   
Limitation of Liability If the client company decides to use the services of another company to operate and provide this company with his / her personal data, the customer should know that safety is his / her personal data are the responsibility of another company, as well. Before another company offers personal data, the client should read the privacy policy. The company's website is online and may have to be linked to other Web sites for customers to be cautious and remember that the company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

#### Use of Cookies 

#### 

To ensure the effective operation of the company's website and client trading activity, the Company will use cookies. Cookies are small text files sent from the company Web server to the client computer. Cookies are used by the company not contain any personal data, account numbers and passwords. The Company may occur other organizations in the management of the site and the collection and analysis of statistical data. Such organizations can establish themselves and their own cookies on behalf of society, such as cookies and shall not contain personal information.   

#### Communication 

#### 

During registration the customer a letter by e-mail confirming their registration. The company can provide information about changes and new promotions for its customers by e-mail or receive e-mails with questions and requests from its customers, and such information is not confidential. By adopting this policy, the customer the company to receive information from the customer by e-mail, including various ideas, methods, products and marketing know-how, without incurring any obligations of the Company. An exception is the customer identification data. The Company is entitled to his store to return or delete correspondence with the customer's discretion. The Company is authorized to follow up on internal communications from customers for the purpose of improving the quality of their services. 

#### Changes in the Privacy Policy 

#### 

Sometimes the company will update its privacy policy. carried out if significant changes in policy, new data protection laws are immediately published on the website of the Company and all clients are informed about the changes. The company recommends that customers read the Privacy Policy from time to time to be aware of how their data is used.
